<xml xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml"><block type="component_event" id="D{O?jSl0PXN6u~KHj8_" x="199" y="101"><mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" component_name="Club Wide Forum" component_type="Screen" parent_id="undefined" event_id="Opens" was_updated="true"/><field name="component_id">a3e16afe-a982-47d0-abca-cf141f1db247</field><field name="event_id">Opens</field><statement name="input_do"><block type="setter" id="(cFCE=lS-Fgz_8$_=Ih9"><mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" component_name="Message List" parent_id="undefined"/><field name="component_id">0bbaa61e-b2a8-49a9-9275-402666ccf68a</field><field name="field_name">TextItems</field><value name="field_value"><block type="lists_split" id=".^)=HuV^VLx|4eEk*f`*"><mutation mode="SPLIT"/><field name="MODE">SPLIT</field><value name="INPUT"><block type="variables_get_dynamic" id="imq=t}XiNbz(蚜甏恝炯骈屐钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰闰译嫩鹛リ讽蒽，骖铁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰秸迕庚袍囝平担惰挽⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰曰淄第闲同笪香耦芍稷炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰蛏熟ビ翟饽抹な胪寓炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰筋ｇ荔猃抟趟挚珑銮盛炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰呐躺廷炯箬徜秣豉疱舰翦簪殇舰赙裹蜓晤瀣谕筵┈冲⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕浼骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰泔眇镱孱暨弼孱簪殇舰邋型帛毖声鲧什坳棉舰舶耿舰吵并炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰渝钿泔眇镱孱暨豉疱舰迈趑镱疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃弼孱暨殇舰渺殂擘麽筮躔溽翦浣Ⅳ蝓澧炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕傅羔岵抖宄舵窗便岫插档獬辈刀蛋涞集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰弼孱暨殇⒕渺殂爰骈屐渚俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰轭瘐暨滹⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰を髁垫嘛蒗啸锱饴７厕⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰鞔乖幅侯臂蕞拐龄牾冖炯骈屐钺礤舰闲⒕闻鸭骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰箦暨珏簪殇舰庀府喻锚请哺胞遛荒谟⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰湾篌徵澧疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕愠钒潮涠徕驽翠岣狗逛枫宓悴撤獾虫集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰骈屐溥钺礤⒕藻艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵铛祆殇舰续镑觖采二镶鲐篾孽炯鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿炯忪镢豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛姊殇舰骆惆画扯锂嘏透兄馥英炯眭翎糸镱屐箦舰雹炯鲠祯钺礤舰善阿炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰ō蕉鼓傍僵娃è与阗踝⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕叛集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏暨澌钺黹恽殇舰脯喹渫咐伏ペ觏漭耿炯骈屐钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰闰译嫩鹛リ讽蒽，骖铁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰退掊剃区赠阄仇舷⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰缜旦泸覃锒ǎ突磐摺蔻炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰瘵瘢｝涿铉吻祀矢珏蔻炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰党嗳ム抽谥俑搽赏挨⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵铛祆殇舰ㄐ÷厌恋卺蝴悫帑垄炯鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦暨澌钺黹恽殇舰诳熨翕仓髭鹨粢唣漂油⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰朦塍从睾掉撩悛峡谑鞯⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰祁锈箧嗌套ㄤ尸酶骤铫炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰盎坟楞膨徼钊烈服ふ⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰楱廴籽碜搿唣诎缅儋⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰傍‘蛩酵堆氙阅男幕纰炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰屁柑森杲俨材钨群林⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒈炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰国沁妩翕哩纯源Ｆ辎炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏暨澌钺黹恽殇舰胩迎悟附泵叉众蝗孤⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰醑世耗瓣匡弈篝珏ǖ虎炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰眢晰壳猓照蠼寥幺砍冖炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰述晒甜癫浏飧榉遽簟余⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕阵弪蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰簖福澄纳榛督奘亩棰炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾躞弪赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静扯徭溽腑洳蛋存愕傅涠颁档浞党层钩集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰陉绒厍嫡惯羔夂帙垄炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕吾礤集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰酣蛏邈髫嗾乖模馆蛘盛炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦暨珏簪殇舰纾蚨侃断涩悴赌贲谒⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰湾篌徵澧疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕愠钒潮涠徕驽翠岣狗逛枫宓悴撤獾虫集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰骈屐溥钺礤⒕藻艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦暨澌钺黹恽殇舰怎忍囝锬栝搞圣噶瞰あ炯骈屐钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰朦塍从睾掉撩悛峡谑鞯⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰梢熏汗秣拱农鸟箢山寓炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰酲＃跎僭坦氓绵蛩胍颏⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰赇琛ｕóィ雄瘤漱⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰搭缗蕲稆聘彻绽痍殉觫炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰涿厢仨嗡搪┴增じ⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏暨澌钺黹恽殇舰谠锕瘕邂含庾白乩⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰闰译嫩鹛リ讽蒽，骖铁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰鹑夸润诮〉蛱回磨睥炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰鹏部松返皴飘争缔味⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰┵洞蹭忉厮武踌短诎垄炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰熵ビ售磊侣黏归秫ヘ⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰藩弁蹊馗敦哗磔媳挞炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕浼骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰批位惶藏蚤蝾休嗒素啖炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏暨澌钺黹恽殇舰ム砌盅析偃战岚拚⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰醑世耗瓣匡弈篝珏ǖ虎炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰索丸狁螵猢痹农獐蛴袼⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰浙≌柘爹镏丑唁酵舨桁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕阵弪蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰雄百闽宰墟时煅门⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾躞弪赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静扯徭溽腑洳蛋存愕傅涠颁档浞党层钩集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰审骠恹篑孑グ亭怄壑⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕吾礤集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰腩揎厥蓰鼬幞颟戟驽舰炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦暨珏簪殇舰戚斜嵝宾猥哎盘秘酡炯眭翎糸镱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰湾篌徵澧疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕愠钒潮涠徕驽翠岣狗逛枫宓悴撤獾虫集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰骈屐溥钺礤⒕藻艏骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦趑弪殇舰玻钻澶呓蜥守饺恃愉⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰湾篌徵涕篝疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕扳忉岫卞獠岣垂峁共返窗捕抖沣娑羔集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰骈屐溥钺礤⒕藻羯翦眢集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰骈屐溥鲠祯澧炯忪镢豉疱舰扉篝筮箴扉簪殇舰聍仨嗷苑扮睑粝联丨⒕柬豸狒轱盹溴舰有躺寓炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕有躺约骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰晌姓寓炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏暨澌钺黹恽殇舰胡鳎孵祷蒌魂琬诠癔⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰用闲泞久滔漳集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰瘟团⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰闰译嫩鹛リ讽蒽，骖铁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕钺礤集骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨觑轭殇舰罡颔琛咏笪芜击苇聊蔻炯眭翎糸镱轸屙蠼⒊炯鲠祯钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰寨睢佚阴峡煌罔癌⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱蟑集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰渥搽ク笆洳滟村ó掎⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱筢鲥溥钺礤舰狃鲠蜷徕戾沆踱赡炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧静钡幢充姝吹赴闯哺獯邋舛卑涔躲浒暗集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰翦簪殇舰嗟讳潆巷笥驱┓掰半胱⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕渺踱骑蝓砑骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰呐躺廷炯箬徜秣豉疱舰翦簪殇舰火驵脐虮仟矾埋冯覆症炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦⒕浼骈屐渚集箬徜秣炯鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦趑弪殇舰障钎鼾谠朵瘵粲打续⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱泔眇镱孱暨钺礤舰湾篌徵澧疳蝈铘唛浣Ⅴ钿彐轭邃炯骈屐钺礤舰泔眇镱孱暨殇⒕愠钒潮涠徕驽翠岣狗逛枫宓悴撤獾虫集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰骈屐溥钺礤⒕藻艏骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰骈屐溥鲠祯澧炯箬徜秣豉疱舰翦簪殇舰揩愁椒槠宿踊枪笤颌炯骈屐钺礤舰耘卦炯箬徜秣炯鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集盱